<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <MF_Flavor_Start_0>a lineage with distinct signs of external intervention. The physical structure of these beings is entirely dictated by the specifics of their origin.</MF_Flavor_Start_0>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_1>stands out from base forms due to its unusual physiology. Traces of deep biological restructuring are visible in their appearance.</MF_Flavor_Start_1>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_2>beings whose appearance directly reflects their genetic history. Every detail of their body is subject to the internal logic of the species' development.</MF_Flavor_Start_2>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_3>indicate their complete adaptation to their niche. Their appearance is devoid of accidental traits, being the result of long selection.</MF_Flavor_Start_3>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_4>differ significantly from standard individuals. Their proportions and tissue structure follow an altered genetic blueprint.</MF_Flavor_Start_4>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_5>a specialized branch whose appearance immediately distinguishes them from others. The biology of these beings was fine-tuned for specific tasks.</MF_Flavor_Start_5>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_6>the result of a consistent modification of the original foundation. In their appearance, functionality completely prevails over aesthetics.</MF_Flavor_Start_6>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_7>possess a characteristic set of external features. Their physical type was shaped under the influence of factors that altered their nature.</MF_Flavor_Start_7>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_8>give the impression of beings whose organism has undergone a complete revision. Their entire appearance points to a departure from primary standards.</MF_Flavor_Start_8>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_9>a group with a unique morphology. Their physical "self" is shaped under the influence of a specific and complex code.</MF_Flavor_Start_9>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_10>unique in a combination of traits that are rarely found together in such an order.</MF_Flavor_Start_10>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_11>bear clear imprints of different lineages, creating a truly original image.</MF_Flavor_Start_11>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_12>represent a living example of how the most diverse external features can intertwine.</MF_Flavor_Start_12>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_13>part of a complex mosaic assembled from the heritage of different ancestors.</MF_Flavor_Start_13>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_14>stand out precisely because of how characteristics taken from different sides coexist within them.</MF_Flavor_Start_14>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_15>possess a recognizable yet completely non-standard set of external characteristics.</MF_Flavor_Start_15>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_16>another reminder of the complexity and richness of biology.</MF_Flavor_Start_16>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_17>is the result of an accidental or intentional combination of different visual markers.</MF_Flavor_Start_17>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_18>cannot be fitted to any single standard due to the abundance of mixed traits.</MF_Flavor_Start_18>
  <MF_Flavor_Start_19>possess an appearance that emphasizes their intermediate position between familiar types.</MF_Flavor_Start_19>

  <MF_Flavor_Connect_0>Their nervous system and sensory organs have specific settings. This leaves its mark on their perception of the world and daily habits.</MF_Flavor_Connect_0>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_1>Internal processes in their bodies flow at a special rhythm. Such biology makes their organism extremely sensitive to the stability of internal balance.</MF_Flavor_Connect_1>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_2>The way the organism interacts with external stimuli is unique. This is due to a deep restructuring of all basic life-support systems.</MF_Flavor_Connect_2>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_3>The metabolism of this branch functions in a specific mode. This makes their life cycles directly dependent on certain biological factors.</MF_Flavor_Connect_3>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_4>The internal chemistry of these beings has been subjected to serious adjustment. This is reflected in their general condition and ways of responding to the environment.</MF_Flavor_Connect_4>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_5>Energy distribution in their bodies follows different rules than standard species. Such a structure requires a special resource recovery regime.</MF_Flavor_Connect_5>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_6>Organs and tissues possess specific properties embedded at the code level. This makes their biology complex and requiring constant attention.</MF_Flavor_Connect_6>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_7>The life cycle of this lineage has its own characteristic features. All body systems work according to internal settings written in the genome.</MF_Flavor_Connect_7>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_8>The organism uses specific mechanisms to maintain life. This has led to the emergence of a unique set of internal needs.</MF_Flavor_Connect_8>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_9>The internal structure of these beings is subject to the principle of narrow specialization. Any change in metabolism is immediately reflected in their condition.</MF_Flavor_Connect_9>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_10>Such a combination of characteristics creates a unique internal balance inherent only to this specific lineage.</MF_Flavor_Connect_10>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_11>The interaction of different traits within a single organism has made their nature unlike the parental foundations.</MF_Flavor_Connect_11>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_12>Their entire set of features works as a unified system, despite the different origins of individual traits.</MF_Flavor_Connect_12>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_13>Even minor changes in their code have led to them being perceived as something completely new.</MF_Flavor_Connect_13>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_14>Their nature is a fragile or, conversely, successful balance between what they inherited from different sides.</MF_Flavor_Connect_14>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_15>The mixing of foundations has led to the emergence of an individual set of needs and internal qualities.</MF_Flavor_Connect_15>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_16>The internal structure of these beings now follows its own logic, dictated by this union.</MF_Flavor_Connect_16>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_17>Every trait they adopted became part of their new, individual biological history.</MF_Flavor_Connect_17>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_18>Their organism adapted to this set of traits, turning them into a stable personal feature.</MF_Flavor_Connect_18>
  <MF_Flavor_Connect_19>This combination of genes has made their existence separate from the rules by which their ancestors live.</MF_Flavor_Connect_19>

  <MF_Flavor_End_0>Due to their biological distinctness, they often face social distance. The attitude toward them from other groups is rarely unambiguous.</MF_Flavor_End_0>
  <MF_Flavor_End_1>In most worlds, they are valued for their unique qualities but rarely accepted into the mainstream. They remain a group living by its own laws.</MF_Flavor_End_1>
  <MF_Flavor_End_2>The presence of these beings often causes wariness in others. Unusual appearance and habits become the cause of misunderstanding by neighbors.</MF_Flavor_End_2>
  <MF_Flavor_End_3>For many, they remain merely a living result of code manipulation. Such status leaves its mark on their relationships with other species.</MF_Flavor_End_3>
  <MF_Flavor_End_4>They occupy a niche where their features become a key factor. Despite this, their lives often pass in relative isolation.</MF_Flavor_End_4>
  <MF_Flavor_End_5>The reputation of this lineage is built on a mixture of facts and speculation. Few dare to ignore their presence, knowing their specific nature.</MF_Flavor_End_5>
  <MF_Flavor_End_6>The history of this branch is full of evidence of their difficult path. In many cultures, they are viewed as an example of how plastic the living essence is.</MF_Flavor_End_6>
  <MF_Flavor_End_7>They rarely fit into standard social structures. Their lifestyle is dictated by biology, which requires a special attitude toward their needs.</MF_Flavor_End_7>
  <MF_Flavor_End_8>They are treated as necessary but extremely specific members of communities. Their capabilities arouse interest, but their nature remains a mystery.</MF_Flavor_End_8>
  <MF_Flavor_End_9>In the eyes of most, they are living proof of the deep changes sweeping the sector. They continue their journey, relying on their unique identity.</MF_Flavor_End_9>
  <MF_Flavor_End_10>Ultimately, they remain themselves — a unique result that cannot be repeated twice.</MF_Flavor_End_10>
  <MF_Flavor_End_11>It is precisely this mixture of traits that makes them noticeable in any society, standing out from the mass of familiar types.</MF_Flavor_End_11>
  <MF_Flavor_End_12>One way or another, they take their place in the world as completely independent and original individuals.</MF_Flavor_End_12>
  <MF_Flavor_End_13>To others, they will forever remain a mystery that cannot be fully solved through their origin.</MF_Flavor_End_13>
  <MF_Flavor_End_14>Their path is a story of how something absolutely unpredictable can arise from familiar elements.</MF_Flavor_End_14>
  <MF_Flavor_End_15>In the eyes of the world, they are living proof that any combination of traits has a right to exist.</MF_Flavor_End_15>
  <MF_Flavor_End_16>Despite all questions about their origin, they continue to live by their own standards.</MF_Flavor_End_16>
  <MF_Flavor_End_17>Their place in the general order of things is determined by this very uniqueness they carry within.</MF_Flavor_End_17>
  <MF_Flavor_End_18>In the end, they are not just a sum of traits, but something more, possessing its own face.</MF_Flavor_End_18>
  <MF_Flavor_End_19>For this reason, they have finally secured the status of beings whose individuality stands above any classifications.</MF_Flavor_End_19>

</LanguageData>