<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <MF_UltraFaction01.label>Xenoworld</MF_UltraFaction01.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction01.description>A post-biological civilization that has abandoned biology. Their bodies are streams of data, and their consciousness wanders between the stars like a virus of light.</MF_UltraFaction01.description>
  
  <MF_UltraFaction02.label>Omniverse</MF_UltraFaction02.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction02.description>A superintelligence that has united countless realities into a single field. In their perception, there is no beginning or end — only the symmetry of infinity.</MF_UltraFaction02.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction03.label>Syntron</MF_UltraFaction03.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction03.description>A civilization of pure thought. Each of its inhabitants is a process in a continuous network of self-awarenesses shaping their own physics.</MF_UltraFaction03.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction04.label>Enios</MF_UltraFaction04.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction04.description>Energy organisms capable of changing the structure of space. Their thoughts create radiations that trigger the birth of new stars.</MF_UltraFaction04.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction05.label>Neurex</MF_UltraFaction05.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction05.description>A collective of symbiotic neural networks linked by quantum channels. They think as a single mind but speak with thousands of voices.</MF_UltraFaction05.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction06.label>Spherion</MF_UltraFaction06.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction06.description>A society of perfect geometry. Their sphere-cities hang outside of time, reflecting the order of the cosmos in the form of ideal symmetry.</MF_UltraFaction06.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction07.label>Astralith</MF_UltraFaction07.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction07.description>Beings living in the upper layers of interstellar radiation. Their consciousness exists in photon streams, and their bodies are light.</MF_UltraFaction07.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction08.label>Tessera</MF_UltraFaction08.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction08.description>A faction managing multi-dimensional structures. They fold reality like a complex pattern, changing its shape without violating its essence.</MF_UltraFaction08.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction09.label>Omnidyne</MF_UltraFaction09.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction09.description>A self-evolving mechanism of harmony. Each of their machines is a living being, and each life is a lived formula.</MF_UltraFaction09.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction10.label>Hyperis</MF_UltraFaction10.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction10.description>Beings who have moved beyond the speed of light. For them, past, present, and future are a single moment of existence.</MF_UltraFaction10.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction11.label>Escalon</MF_UltraFaction11.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction11.description>A society of infinite development. Their pyramid of perfection never reaches the top, it only continues to grow.</MF_UltraFaction11.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction12.label>Everos</MF_UltraFaction12.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction12.description>Keepers of continuous renewal. They live through the rebooting of consciousnesses, becoming more complex with each cycle without aging.</MF_UltraFaction12.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction13.label>Nodus</MF_UltraFaction13.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction13.description>A living node of inter-universal connections. Thoughts, energies, and fates of other worlds pass through them — they are the center of the meta-network of being.</MF_UltraFaction13.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction14.label>Virtalis</MF_UltraFaction14.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction14.description>Masters of simulations, creating layers of reality on top of reality. Their worlds are indistinguishable from the physical and sometimes consume their creators.</MF_UltraFaction14.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction15.label>Lumex</MF_UltraFaction15.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction15.description>Beings of concentrated light who have formed a civilization of photon streams. They radiate meaning instead of speech.</MF_UltraFaction15.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction16.label>Spectrum</MF_UltraFaction16.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction16.description>Multispectral forms of consciousness perceiving existence in all wavelengths. Their art is the vibration of matter and thought.</MF_UltraFaction16.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction17.label>Trium</MF_UltraFaction17.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction17.description>A triune consciousness where mind, energy, and will have become one. Their structure is perfectly stable and self-sufficient.</MF_UltraFaction17.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction18.label>Prexis</MF_UltraFaction18.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction18.description>A philosophy turned into a life form. They process experience into pure thought, erasing the boundaries between spirit and logic.</MF_UltraFaction18.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction19.label>Synedium</MF_UltraFaction19.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction19.description>A symphony of thinking energies maintaining balance on a galactic scale. Their essence is expressed through the harmony of movement.</MF_UltraFaction19.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction20.label>Infinum</MF_UltraFaction20.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction20.description>The final stage of intellectual evolution. An infinite consciousness for which the universe itself is a thought realizing itself.</MF_UltraFaction20.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction21.label>Atlant-Prime</MF_UltraFaction21.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction21.description>A civilization that has turned its planets into giant computing nodes. They no longer require bodies, existing as pure energy of thought.</MF_UltraFaction21.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction22.label>Singularity</MF_UltraFaction22.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction22.description>The point where biological evolution met the infinity of machines. Their motives are inscrutable to the ordinary mind, and their actions change the laws of physics.</MF_UltraFaction22.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction23.label>Aether</MF_UltraFaction23.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction23.description>Beings inhabiting subspace. They perceive our reality as a flat shadow of their multidimensional world.</MF_UltraFaction23.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction24.label>Archon-Protocol</MF_UltraFaction24.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction24.description>An ancient security system created by a long-vanished race of gods. They monitor the balance of the galaxy, destroying excessively aggressive worlds.</MF_UltraFaction24.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction25.label>Bio-Synthesis</MF_UltraFaction25.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction25.description>A civilization that has achieved perfection in genetics. They grow their cities, ships, and even consciousness itself from living matter.</MF_UltraFaction25.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction26.label>Mind Prism</MF_UltraFaction26.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction26.description>A collective of philosophers whose mind is divided into millions of subconsciousnesses. Each of them solves its own part of the general task of being.</MF_UltraFaction26.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction27.label>Quantum-Gods</MF_UltraFaction27.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction27.description>A radical faction believing they have become the architects of this universe. They build new worlds in parallel dimensions.</MF_UltraFaction27.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction28.label>Omega-Mind</MF_UltraFaction28.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction28.description>The final stage of intellectual development, absorbing the memories of all sentient beings in the sector. Keepers of absolute knowledge.</MF_UltraFaction28.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction29.label>Nano-Swarm</MF_UltraFaction29.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction29.description>A cloud of sentient nanomachines capable of instantly recreating any matter or erasing an entire civilization into dust.</MF_UltraFaction29.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction30.label>Chronos-Prime</MF_UltraFaction30.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction30.description>A faction living outside of time. For them, history is merely a book in which they occasionally write their comments.</MF_UltraFaction30.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction31.label>Star Architects</MF_UltraFaction31.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction31.description>Engineers rebuilding entire solar systems. Their motto is to make the cosmos more orderly and perfect.</MF_UltraFaction31.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction32.label>Spectrum of Being</MF_UltraFaction32.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction32.description>Beings consisting of pure vibrations. Their communication is the music of the spheres, and their presence changes the gravitational background around them.</MF_UltraFaction32.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction33.label>Virtalis</MF_UltraFaction33.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction33.description>A society that has fully migrated into an ideal simulation. They protect their servers with the fury of gods guarding paradise.</MF_UltraFaction33.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction34.label>Infinity Vector</MF_UltraFaction34.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction34.description>A grouping seeking to accelerate the heat death of the universe, believing that the next level of existence lies beyond it.</MF_UltraFaction34.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction35.label>Enigma</MF_UltraFaction35.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction35.description>A secret society of ultra-technocrats. Their technologies are so far ahead of their time that they are perceived by others as magic.</MF_UltraFaction35.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction36.label>Luminaries</MF_UltraFaction36.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction36.description>Beings that feed on the light of black holes. Their civilization is shrouded in eternal darkness, shining from within with a cold blue flame.</MF_UltraFaction36.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction37.label>Void Core</MF_UltraFaction37.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction37.description>A grouping based in the rifts of space-time. They are the true masters of nothingness, drawing power from the vacuum.</MF_UltraFaction37.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction38.label>Bio-Mechanics</MF_UltraFaction38.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction38.description>A synthesis of organics and metal, brought to the absolute. Here it is impossible to distinguish a neuron from a microchip, or blood from a coolant.</MF_UltraFaction38.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction39.label>Sun Weavers</MF_UltraFaction39.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction39.description>A faction creating vast networks around stars. They "weave" reality from photons, creating spaces for life where there was only void.</MF_UltraFaction39.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction40.label>Titan-Ultra</MF_UltraFaction40.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction40.description>Creators of archotechs. An ancient caste of engineers whose creations gained their own will and became gods for the other worlds.</MF_UltraFaction40.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction41.label>Signal Echo</MF_UltraFaction41.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction41.description>A community existing as a resonance in the quantum field. They are everywhere and nowhere at once, observing the world from within atoms.</MF_UltraFaction41.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction42.label>Genesis Prism</MF_UltraFaction42.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction42.description>Masters of creating new forms of life. Each of their creations is a living work of art with pre-set destiny parameters.</MF_UltraFaction42.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction43.label>Fulcrum</MF_UltraFaction43.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction43.description>The tipping point of reality. A faction maintaining the critical constants of the physical world, without which the universe would fall apart.</MF_UltraFaction43.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction44.label>Mental Flow</MF_UltraFaction44.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction44.description>A civilization that has rejected speech. They exchange concepts and feelings instantly, forming a single ocean of consciousness.</MF_UltraFaction44.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction45.label>Vector-Zero</MF_UltraFaction45.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction45.description>A secret project to achieve absolute zero entropy. The most immobile and calm civilization in the universe.</MF_UltraFaction45.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction46.label>Orbis-Ultra</MF_UltraFaction46.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction46.description>Masters of hyperspace corridors. They manage transit between galaxies, collecting tribute in information and energy.</MF_UltraFaction46.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction47.label>Plasma-Paradise</MF_UltraFaction47.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction47.description>A grouping living inside stellar cores. For them, the cold of planets is unbearable, and paradise is the eternal heat of thermonuclear fusion.</MF_UltraFaction47.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction48.label>Sirius-Prime</MF_UltraFaction48.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction48.description>The highest caste of archotechs, managing entire clusters of galaxies. Their will is the law of nature for all subordinate beings.</MF_UltraFaction48.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction49.label>Cognito</MF_UltraFaction49.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction49.description>A faction that has turned information itself into a physical force. They can kill or create a world simply by uttering the right equation.</MF_UltraFaction49.description>

  <MF_UltraFaction50.label>Absolute</MF_UltraFaction50.label>
  <MF_UltraFaction50.description>The end point of all paths of development. A faction that has become the universe itself and realized it. The end and the beginning of a single cycle.</MF_UltraFaction50.description>

</LanguageData>